<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>whatsnew on RISU</title><link>https://risuorg.github.io/tags/whatsnew/</link><description>Recent content in whatsnew on RISU</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 07:50:38 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://risuorg.github.io/tags/whatsnew/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Risu: What's new? 2020-06-11</title><link>https://risuorg.github.io/post/2020-06-11-whatsnew/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 Jun 2020 07:50:38 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://risuorg.github.io/post/2020-06-11-whatsnew/</guid><description>What&amp;rsquo;s new? Other posts in this category: What&amp;rsquo;s new
General Extra plugin tree support: allows to specify alternate plugin tree (in addition to internal one) so that Risu can be integrated more easily with other solutions (for example, excluding Risuclient plugins and just listing the ones in the additional folder) Some minor fixes in documentation and plugins New logo!</description></item><item><title>Risu: What's new? 2019-09-13</title><link>https://risuorg.github.io/post/2019-09-13-whatsnew/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Sep 2019 07:50:38 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://risuorg.github.io/post/2019-09-13-whatsnew/</guid><description>What&amp;rsquo;s new? Other posts in this category: What&amp;rsquo;s new
General Pie charts are now shown for profile reports, showing one &amp;lsquo;piece&amp;rsquo; for each status of plugins reported, check www preview for a sample.</description></item><item><title>Risu: What's new? 2019-08-16</title><link>https://risuorg.github.io/post/2019-08-16-whatsnew/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Aug 2019 07:25:38 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://risuorg.github.io/post/2019-08-16-whatsnew/</guid><description>What&amp;rsquo;s new? Other posts in this category: What&amp;rsquo;s new
General Improve handling of dates forcing LC_ALL Create a new function (thanks Mikel) to take from an ordered list of files the first_file_available and exits (because sometimes, depending on sosreport version it might have one file or another). Patternfly was updated to latest minor Other changes made to is_active and is_enabled Functions that were later enhanced to use first_file_available Test to detect issues with LEAPP in-place upgrade for EL7-&amp;gt;EL8 if / and /var are on different device.</description></item><item><title>Risu 1.0.0 released!!</title><link>https://risuorg.github.io/post/2019-01-01-risu-v1.0.0/</link><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 12:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://risuorg.github.io/post/2019-01-01-risu-v1.0.0/</guid><description>During the las months Risu team has not found any big issues or functionality that could be missed and worked mostly on performance improvements and some other tests.
It was a good timing to align a new year with official release of Risu 1.0.0.
We&amp;rsquo;ve recently also embraced a new telegram chat for our users via https://t.me/RisuUG to contact our team and for driving further development and evolution.
Join us in celebrating 2009 with a new full set of opportunities and challenges to rise up!</description></item><item><title>Risu: Your system at a glance</title><link>https://risuorg.github.io/post/2018-08-24-your-system-at-a-glance/</link><pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2018 23:23:58 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://risuorg.github.io/post/2018-08-24-your-system-at-a-glance/</guid><description>What&amp;rsquo;s new? Other posts in this category: What&amp;rsquo;s new
System information summary Thanks to the suggestion of a colleague, we&amp;rsquo;ve added &amp;lsquo;sysinfo&amp;rsquo; as a &amp;lsquo;profile&amp;rsquo;.
The idea of this, together with the RC_INFO code introduced is to leverage some scripts that report information relevant to the system being analyzed, that might or not be a problem, but still gives you context information about what you&amp;rsquo;re trying to diagnose.
Based on this, and by adjusting sysinfo.</description></item><item><title>Risu: What's new? 2018-07-08</title><link>https://risuorg.github.io/post/2018-07-08-whatsnew/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Jul 2018 18:25:38 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://risuorg.github.io/post/2018-07-08-whatsnew/</guid><description>What&amp;rsquo;s new? Other posts in this category: What&amp;rsquo;s new
General anonymizaton We&amp;rsquo;ve moved this to an independent function and updated the &amp;lsquo;&amp;ndash;call-home &amp;rsquo; to use this function (but leaving sosreport path), so that the results can be aggregated later for checking trends on rules detecting issues, etc. metrics As part of above change, we&amp;rsquo;ve started a small spinoff that we want to integrate back into Nexus on grabbing metrics of execution we can later analyze.</description></item><item><title>Risu: What's new? 2018-07-02</title><link>https://risuorg.github.io/post/2018-07-02-whatsnew/</link><pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2018 18:25:38 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://risuorg.github.io/post/2018-07-02-whatsnew/</guid><description>What&amp;rsquo;s new? Other posts in this category: What&amp;rsquo;s new
General RC_INFO We had discussions in the past about info that we could provide that was not really a Error. After some extra feedback we did add the RC_INFO exit code to the tests, so that for example xsos output is also provided with Risu results so that it can be quickly checked also from the Web UI overrides.json Allows to override fields in the results json with some values, for example to force updates of the titles, urls, etc in the results returned.</description></item><item><title>Risu featured on redhat.com blog</title><link>https://risuorg.github.io/post/2018-06-08-rhcomblog/</link><pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 22:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://risuorg.github.io/post/2018-06-08-rhcomblog/</guid><description>Red Hat blog post! Risu has been featured in a blog post at https://www.redhat.com/en/blog/Risu-system-configuration-validation-tool?scid=701f2000000tnTlAAI
where we highlight what you already know!
Happy reading!</description></item><item><title>Recent changes in Magui and Risu</title><link>https://risuorg.github.io/post/2018-05-08-whatsnew/</link><pubDate>Tue, 08 May 2018 07:17:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://risuorg.github.io/post/2018-05-08-whatsnew/</guid><description>What&amp;rsquo;s new? Our previous edition of What&amp;rsquo;s new was stored externally at https://iranzo.github.io/blog/2018/01/16/recent-changes-in-magui-and-Risu/, so we&amp;rsquo;ve copied to this website for completeness (now locally at: Whats new)
What has happened since then?
We&amp;rsquo;re presenting at SuperSec 2018 in Almería, Spain SuperSec 2018 Up to 217 plugins as of today Lot of code changes Some of the changes include&amp;hellip;
General New domain: https://Risuorg.github.io and new URL for repos https://github.com/Risuorg/
Updated presentation files</description></item><item><title>Recent changes in Magui and Risu</title><link>https://risuorg.github.io/post/2018-01-16-recent-changes-in-magui-and-risu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2018 21:17:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://risuorg.github.io/post/2018-01-16-recent-changes-in-magui-and-risu/</guid><description>What&amp;rsquo;s new? During recent weeks we&amp;rsquo;ve been coding and performing several changes to Risu and Magui.
Checking the latest logs or list of issues open and closed on github is probably not an easy task or the best way to get &amp;lsquo;up-to-date&amp;rsquo; with changes, so I&amp;rsquo;ll try to compile a few here.
First of all, we&amp;rsquo;re going to present it at Devconf.cz 2018, so come stop-by if assisting :-)
Some of the changes include&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Timeline</title><link>https://risuorg.github.io/changelog/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Jun 2016 17:27:47 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://risuorg.github.io/changelog/</guid><description>Changelog hilights This file will contain a manually mantained log of hilights between versions, it&amp;rsquo;s not a very extensive detail, but some of the bigger changes/ideas will be added here.
Check What&amp;rsquo;s new: tag for more updated information.
2018-03-25 Implement --find to Risu so that it can grep across a folder set for checking historic data for tests. 2018-03-18 Magui autogrouping support, generating files for each comparison set like osp roles, same hostname, etc.</description></item></channel></rss>